Scratch that bring it back (Shook! Shook! Ha)
When I’m in front of you Glitch Mode
Glitch Mode di depanmu
君の前では Glitch Mode
네 앞에선 Glitch Mode
ต่อหน้าเธอ Glitch Mode
在你面前 Glitch Mode
Đối diện với em Glitch Mode
My whole body freezes Reload
Seluruh tubuhku hancur Reload
体がイカれてる Reload
온몸이 고장 났어 Reload
ร่างกายฉัน หนาวสั่นไปทั้งตัว Reload
全身出现故障 Reload
Toàn thân anh như đông cứng lại Reload
My head is spinning spinning Migraine
Aku pusing pusing pusing sakit kepala
僕はクラクラ頭痛
난 어질 어질 어질 두통
เวียนหัว เวียนหัว เวียนหัว
我迷迷糊糊 头痛
Chóng mặt, đau đầu lại chóng mặt
Again and again, Iʼm in Glitch Mode
Iʼm in Glitch Mode lagi dan lagi
また巡り巡って　Iʼm in Glitch Mode
또 돌고 돌아 Iʼm in Glitch Mode
หันกลับมาอีกครั้ง Iʼm in Glitch Mode
我晕头转向 Iʼm in Glitch Mode
Lại quay lại quay Iʼm in Glitch Mode
Never happened Situation
Situation yang belum pernah terjadi
これまでなかった Situation
전에 없던 Situation
Situation ไม่เคยเป็นมาก่อน
前所未有的 Situation
Chưa từng có tiền lệ Situation
You or only you Repetition
Kau atau hanya kau Repetition
君　いや　君だけ Repetition
너 아님 너만 Repetition
ไม่ใช่เธอเท่านั้น Repetition
是你 只有你 Repetition
Em, không phải, chỉ mỗi em thôi Repetition
Trouble trouble like a miscode
Emergency alert
Berada dalam keadaan darurat
非常事態発生
비상이 걸려
มีเหตุฉุกเฉิน
心中响起警报
Báo động khẩn cấp
Bu--buffering
Sedang bu.. buffering
バッ、　バッファリングだ
버 버퍼링이야
มันเป็นบัฟเฟอร์ริง
正 正在缓冲中
là Buffering đấy
I’m on that Glitch Mode
Dangerous engine Sound
Mesin Sound bahaya
エンジンSound　危ないぞ
엔진 Sound 위험해
Sound ของเครื่องยนต์ที่อันตราย
引擎Sound 危险情况
Sound động cơ nguy hiểm
Never experienced Pit a pat
Tak pernah alami Pit a pat
経験したことないPit a pat
겪은 적 없는 Pit a pat
ไม่เคยเจอมาก่อน Pit a pat
未曾经历过的 Pit a pat
Chưa từng nếm trải Pit a pat
You come closer Whoop! The whoop!
Kau dekatiku Whoop! The whoop!
近づいてくる君　whoop! The whoop!
네가 다가와 Whoop! The whoop!
เธอใกล้เข้ามา Whoop! The whoop!
你在靠近我 whoop! The whoop!
Em bước đến gần Whoop! The whoop!
My breath stops
Kenapa aku tak bisa bernafas
なんで息が止まるんだ
왜 숨이 멎는데
ฉันแทบหยุดหายใจ
为什么我快要窒息
Sao lại ngừng thở
My heartbeat accelerates, Go speeding up
Jantungku berdetak lebih kencang Go speeding up
高鳴る鼓動　Go speeding up
가속도를 타는 심장 Go speeding up
หัวใจเต้นเร็ว Go speeding up
心跳开始加速 Go speeding up
Tim đập liên hồi Go speeding up
This feelings, no words Can’t get enough
Perasaan ini, Can’t get enough dengan kata apapun
この感情　どんな言葉でも Can’t get enough
이 감정은 어떤 말도 Can’t get enough
ความรู้สึกนี้มันคืออะไรกันนะ Can’t get enough
这种心情用任何字眼都Can’t get enough
Cảm giác này không có từ ngữ nào Can’t get enough
Watch me Imma be crazy
Can’t fight this, Hands up
Tak bisa melawan Hands up
抵抗すらできずにHands up
저항도 못하고 Hands up
ไม่กล้าต่อต้าน Hands up
我根本无法抵抗 Hands up
Không thể kháng cự Hands up
Can’t recover, this one-punch Ransom slams Into my mind
Kembalikanlah Into my mind
また振り出しさ　Into my mind
돌이켜 놔 Into my mind
เอาคืนไม่ได้ หมัดนี้ Ransom กระแทก Into my mind
我猝不及防 Into my mind
Trả lại trạng thái ban đầu Into my mind
Can’t recover, this one-punch Ransom slams Into my mind
Ransom yang menyebar dalam satu tembakan
一気に広がる Ransom
한방에 퍼지는 Ransom
เอาคืนไม่ได้ หมัดนี้ Ransom กระแทก Into my mind
迅速扩散的 Ransom
Một cú Ransom dồn dập
Alert, alert,
Kenapa begini kenapa ini kenapa
どうしたんだ一体
왜 이래 왜 이래 왜
ทำไม ทำไม ทำไม
这到底是什么情况
Sao lại như vậy? Sao lại như vậy? Tại sao?
This is a fatal situation
Inilah situasi fatal
これは致命的な事態
이건 치명적인 사태
นี่เป็นสถานการณ์ที่ร้ายแรง
我的系统已经瘫痪
Quả là một đòn chí mạng
Shutting me down, system unresponsive,
Shutting me down tak terkendali
Shutting me down　制御不能
Shutting me down 제어 불가
Shutting me down ควบคุมไม่ได้
Shutting me down 难以自控
Shutting me down không thể kiểm soát
They Say I’m too much
Semuanya Say I’m too much
みんなSay I’m too much
모두 다 Say I’m too much
ทุกคน Say I’m too much
大家都说 Say I’m too much
Mọi người đều Say I’m too much
A sweet rain shower that you’re bringing
Karena hujan indah yang kamu bawa
君が降らす甘いにわか雨に
네가 몰고 오는 달디단 소나기에
เพราะสายฝนแสนหวานที่เธอนำมา
你就像一场甜蜜的雷阵雨
Cơn mưa rào ngọt ngào em dẫn tới
These little sprouts soon become the forest
Tunas kecil tumbuh dan menjadikan hutan
小さな芽が出て森となる
작은 싹이 돋아나 숲을 키워내
ต้นอ่อนน้อยเหล่านี้จะกลายเป็นป่าในไม่ช้า
滋润爱的萌芽 让它茁壮成长
Chồi non chớm nở, sớm trở thành rừng
Growing up to heaven
Touching on the sun
Try as I may, you grow in me
Tak peduli seberapa sering aku menghentikanmu, kamu terus bertumbuh di dalamku
いくら抑えても広がっていくばかり
너를 아무리 아무리 막아도 자라나고
ปิดกั้นเธอเท่าไรมันก็โตขึ้น
无法阻挡你肆意生长
Có cố ngăn cản thì vẫn cứ phát triển
Trouble trouble like a miscode
Emergency alert
Berada dalam keadaan darurat
非常事態発生
비상이 걸려
เกิดเหตุฉุกเฉิน
心中响起警报
Báo động khẩn cấp
I’m on that Glitch Mode
I’m on
Scratch that bring it back (Shook! Shook! Ha)
When I’m in front of you Glitch Mode
Glitch Mode di depanmu
君の前では Glitch Mode
네 앞에선 Glitch Mode
ต่อหน้าเธอ Glitch Mode
在你面前 Glitch Mode
Đối diện với em Glitch Mode
My whole body freezes Reload
Seluruh tubuhku hancur Reload
体がイカれてる Reload
온몸이 고장 났어 Reload
ร่างกายฉัน หนาวสั่นไปทั้งตัว Reload
全身出现故障 Reload
Toàn thân anh như đông cứng lại Reload
My head is spinning spinning Migraine
Aku pusing pusing pusing sakit kepala
僕はクラクラ頭痛
난 어질 어질 어질 두통
เวียนหัว เวียนหัว เวียนหัว
我迷迷糊糊 头痛
Chóng mặt, đau đầu lại chóng mặt
Again and again, Iʼm in Glitch Mode
Iʼm in Glitch Mode lagi dan lagi
また巡り巡って　Iʼm in Glitch Mode
또 돌고 돌아 Iʼm in Glitch Mode
หันกลับมาอีกครั้ง Iʼm in Glitch Mode
我晕头转向 Iʼm in Glitch Mode
Lại quay lại quay Iʼm in Glitch Mode
Never happened Situation
Situation yang belum pernah terjadi
これまでなかった Situation
전에 없던 Situation
Situation ไม่เคยเป็นมาก่อน
前所未有的 Situation
Chưa từng có tiền lệ Situation
You or only you Repetition
Kau atau hanya kau Repetition
君　いや　君だけ Repetition
너 아님 너만 Repetition
ไม่ใช่เธอ เธอเท่านั้น Repetition
是你 只有你 Repetition
Em, không phải, chỉ mỗi em thôi Repetition
Trouble trouble like a miscode
Emergency alert
Berada dalam keadaan darurat
非常事態発生
비상이 걸려
มีเหตุฉุกเฉิน
心中响起警报
Báo động khẩn cấp
Bu--buffering
Sedang bu.. buffering
バッ、　バッファリングだ
버 버퍼링이야
มันเป็นบัฟเฟอร์ริง
正 正在缓冲中
là Buffering đấy
I’m on that Glitch Mode
Code is ‘buffering’, color this Scene
Code is buffering, warnai Scene ini
Code isバッファリング　塗りつぶす　このScene
Code is 버퍼링 칠해 이 Scene
Code is บัฟเฟอร์ริง ทาสี Sceneนี้
Code is 缓冲在 演绎这段Scene
Code is buffering hãy tô màu Scene này
Your beauty is Clickbait going
Kecantikanmu Clickbait going
君の美しさはClickbait going
너의 미모는 Clickbait going
ความงามของเธอ Clickbait going
你的美貌就是Clickbait going
Vẻ đẹp của em Clickbait going
Straight to you Auto pilot in the air
Bagiku Auto pilot in the air
君に Auto pilot in the air
네게 Auto pilot in the air
Auto pilot in the air ต่อเธอ
为你 Auto pilot in the air
Auto pilot in the air tiến đến em
A brand new formula you are
Inilah formula yang belum pernah kulihat sebelumnya
今まで見たことのない数式だけど
어디서도 본 적 없던 수식인 걸
เธอเป็นสูตรที่ไม่เคยเห็นมาก่อน
你是我从没见过的方程式
Một dạng công thức chưa từng có
I can memorize every detail of you
Aku bisa mengingat segala tentangmu
覚えていられる　僕は君のすべてを
외워 둘 수 있어 나는 네 모든 걸
ฉันจำได้ ในทุกๆอย่างของเธอ
但我可以记住关于你的所有代码
Anh có thể ghi nhớ mọi thứ về em
I was dreaming of you the whole night
Aku terjaga sepanjang malam memimpikanmu
君を夢見ながら夜を明かす
너를 꿈꾸느라 밤새
ฝันถึงเธอทั้งคืน
我每天晚上都会梦到你
Cả đêm mơ về em
A dream without you is a Nightmare
Semua mimpi tanpamu adalah Nightmare
君のいない夢は　全部Nightmare
너 없는 꿈은 전부 Nightmare
ความฝันที่ไม่มีเธอ มันเป็น Nightmare
没有你的梦都是 Nightmare
Những giấc mơ không có em đều là Nightmare
Here we go, Glitch mode
Dimulainya Glitch Mode
始まったGlitch Mode
시작된 Glitch Mode
Glitch Mode ที่เริ่มขึ้น
正进入Glitch Mode
Bắt đầu Glitch Mode
No worries, one little error, I like it
Kau tidak perlu terkejut, satu kesalahan tak apa-apa I like it
驚く必要ないんだ　エラーの一つぐらい　I like it
놀라지 않아도 돼 오류 하나쯤 I like it
ไม่ต้องตกใจ สิ่งผิดพลาดเล็กน้อย I like it
不必大惊小怪 这种错误I like it
Đừng hoảng hốt, chút lỗi hệ thống I like it
If this is love, OK
Kalau ini cinta, Ok
これが恋なら　Ok
이런 게 사랑이면 Ok
ถ้านี่คือความรัก Ok
如果这就是爱 Ok
Nếu đây là tình yêu OK
Slightest touch, my mind goes blank
Bahkan sentuhan ujung jari menghentikan pikiranku
指先が触れただけでも　頭の中は真っ白
스친 손끝에도 머릿속이 정지돼
สัมผัสเพียงเล็กน้อย จิตใจก็ว่างเปล่า
只要你轻微触碰 我的大脑就会停止思考
Chỉ một cái chạm lướt qua, đầu óc cũng trở nên đờ đẫn
Unfamiliar senses take over
Perasaan asing mendominasi tubuhku
慣れない感覚が 僕の体を支配する
낯선 감각들이 내 몸을 지배해
ความรู้สึกแปลกๆ เข้าครอบงำร่างกายฉัน
身体会被陌生的感觉支配
Những cảm giác lạ lùng chi phối cơ thể anh
There was no you
There was no me
Emotions are hovering in this Place
Perasaan yang mengitari Place ini
感情だけが漂うPlace
감정만 떠도는 Place
Place ที่มีแต่อารมณ์ล่องลอย
只剩下情感的Place
Nơi chỉ có cảm xúc thăng hoa Place
Everything that’s not you, get Out of the space
Semuanya kecuali kamu, pergi Out of the space
君じゃない　他のものはすべて　Out of the space
너 아닌 다른 모든 건 Out of the space
ทุกสิ่งทุกอย่างยกเว้นเธอ ออกไป Out of the space
除了你其他一切都 Out of the space
Mọi thứ ngoài em đều Out of the space
299,792 per second
Light Speed Bass Drop
Robot Blast Start Off
Scratch that bring it back (Shook! Shook! Ha)
When I’m in front of you Glitch Mode
Glitch Mode di depanmu
君の前では Glitch Mode
네 앞에선 Glitch Mode
ต่อหน้าเธอ Glitch Mode
在你面前 Glitch Mode
Đối diện với em Glitch Mode
My whole body freezes Reload
Seluruh tubuhku hancur Reload
体がイカれてる Reload
온몸이 고장 났어 Reload
ร่างกายฉัน หนาวสั่นไปทั้งตัว Reload
全身出现故障 Reload
Toàn thân anh như đông cứng lại Reload
My head is spinning spinning Migraine
Aku pusing pusing pusing sakit kepala
僕はクラクラ頭痛
난 어질 어질 어질 두통
เวียนหัว เวียนหัว เวียนหัว
我迷迷糊糊 头痛
Chóng mặt, đau đầu lại chóng mặt
Again and again, Iʼm in Glitch Mode
Iʼm in Glitch Mode lagi dan lagi
また巡り巡って　Iʼm in Glitch Mode
또 돌고 돌아 Iʼm in Glitch Mode
หันกลับมาอีกครั้ง Iʼm in Glitch Mode
我晕头转向 Iʼm in Glitch Mode
Lại quay lại quay Iʼm in Glitch Mode
Never happened Situation
Situation yang belum pernah terjadi
これまでなかった Situation
전에 없던 Situation
Situation ไม่เคยเป็นมาก่อน
前所未有的 Situation
Chưa từng có tiền lệ Situation
You or only you Repetition
Kau atau hanya kau Repetition
君　いや　君だけ Repetition
너 아님 너만 Repetition
ไม่ใช่เธอ เธอเท่านั้น Repetition
是你 只有你 Repetition
Em, không phải, chỉ mỗi em thôi Repetition
Trouble trouble like a miscode
Emergency alert
Berada dalam keadaan darurat
非常事態発生
비상이 걸려
มีเหตุฉุกเฉิน
心中响起警报
Báo động khẩn cấp
Bu--buffering
Sedang bu.. buffering
バッ、　バッファリングだ
버 버퍼링이야
มันเป็นบัฟเฟอร์ริง
正 正在缓冲中
là Buffering đấy
I’m on that Glitch Mode